Coming.
Sister Jialin.
Looks like I made a bad deal.
Be a good girl, Yanyan.
Take good care of her.
He can handle it.
Bye-bye.
Kiddo, you have to listen to your
big brother at his house, okay?
If I call you big brother,
shouldn't you call my mom "Auntie"?
Shit!
Sister Lan highly recommends
Director Ou's films.
I want to recommend you for his next movie.
Shipping dynamics are
just a stepping stone for you.
For the long run, you
need a solid portfolio.
"Rumination" won the
Palme d'Or half a year ago.
But it didn't make much
of a splash domestically.
I didn't pay much attention to it.
Director Ou's films have
always been foreign-funded.
They aren't heavily promoted domestically.
The theme of that one
is also quite sensitive.
It's better to avoid unnecessary trouble.
Just quietly winning an award [is fine].
The authorities don't want it
to escalate into public debate.
Opposing human genetic customization.
Is it about sperm bank surrogacy?
Those are two different concepts.
Look it up with AI.
I didn't expect Director Li and
Director Ou to be college classmates.
Yeah, we were college classmates.
But we didn't major in film.
Then what did you major in?
We majored in finance.
Ah.
President Fang, I'm
sincerely inviting Lang Di.
Lang Di has some family issues going on.
Director Li can wait.
I'll definitely save his schedule for you.
Director Ou, let's add
each other on WeChat.
Sure.
I'll scan you.
Okay.
Lu.
You add him too.
You've got skills, little girl.
Are you a girl?
Shouldn't girls play...
games like playing house?
You're so stereotypical.
Shit!
And uncivilized.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm hungry, ordering takeout.
Takeout is expensive. I'll cook for you.
Let you taste the skills
of a top-tier five-star chef.
I don't believe you.
Come here.
Stereotypical.
"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream"
(Episode 14: Vortex)
It's open.
You look okay.
What else can I do if I'm not?
Is everything taken care of?
Yeah.
The process will be a bit troublesome.
Since there's no body, after all.
Can't the body be found?
There are too many
possibilities in a primeval forest.
Where's Mom?
She went to stay at the
temple for a few days.
So President Fang really doesn't
want to make money with me.
President Jin, with your capabilities,
you don't need me to lead the way.
If Han Lu isn't in this drama,
we definitely can't accept your investment.
What if one day you demand Han
Lu join the cast with your funding?
Our company's producers and
directors would definitely flip the table.
I get it. President Fang
doesn't call the shots.
That's exactly how it is.
If you want to produce good
work, you can't be hijacked by capital.
Our company's producers and directors
are the ones calling the shots.
Sister.
Sister Jialin, did I cause
trouble for the company?
Life is just about
getting rid of one trouble
and welcoming the next.
What's Jin Lifeng's background anyway?
The kind you can't look up.
Don't overthink it, focus on the present.
The role of Ran Huang is hard to cast.
Needs a fatherly vibe but can't be old.
Such an actor doesn't exist right now.
Someone who looks young but wise.
If Brother Zhen were 20
years younger, he'd be perfect.
Give it to me.
Okay.
Lu, be careful lately.
It's fine however the fans ship you,
but your cohabitation can't be found out.
Got it.
He's joining a cast soon.
He's away from home lately.
What drama?
It's a political thriller.
There's a lot of room
to showcase his acting.
Sister.
You're busy lately,
leave Zhiyan with me.
Sure.
Yanyan.
Go ahead.
Sister Jialin, give me a ride.
I'm leaving. Be good at home, hear me?
Wait for me to come back.
Bye-bye.
Brother Han Lu.
Dad Qi isn't home.
What should I do if I'm hungry?
Order takeout.
Takeout isn't eco-friendly.
What did you just call him?
Dad Qi.
Then why do you call me brother?
People who can cook are called Dad.
People who can't cook are called Brother.
You little brat.
[On the call: Qi Haoyu]
I have something to tell you.
Speak.
The director added scenes for me.
That's a good thing.
No, it's not.
He added intimate scenes.
I told the company
I only took this role because
there were no romantic scenes.
But the company said
it wasn't in the contract.
If I don't act now, it's
a breach of contract.
How much is the penalty?
Two more magazine's worth.
I suspect someone is
messing with me on purpose.
Why would they mess with you?
Wait for news from me.
Yanyan, let's go out and play. Come on.
Zhiyan, say hello.
Hello, Grandpa.
Am I that old?
I call any man older than my mom "Grandpa."
Kids just say whatever comes to mind.
Please don't take offense, President Jin.
The big star asked me out today.
You must be in a good mood.
Zhiyan, do you want to play in the garden?
Yes.
Go ahead.
President Jin, I heard you want to
invest in our company's new project.
President Fang didn't agree.
You must have spent a
lot pulling other strings.
It's my fault for making
you waste your efforts.
I know you thought highly of me before,
and wanted to invest in me.
But the risks in our industry are too high.
It's easy to get canceled.
Long-term investments aren't very secure.
I suggest you try short-term investments.
Qi Haoyu and I are about to
release a new magazine issue.
If he doesn't film intimate
scenes with anyone else,
the sales of this magazine
will definitely satisfy you.
Do you think I'm short on money?
No, no.
Of course President
Jin isn't short on money.
And certainly not short on people.
I'm just a rookie actor.
I've done everything I can.
President Jin, everything
should be fine now, right?
Coming!
Wow.
You didn't even tell me you were coming.
The door's open.
Open?
My bad.
It really is that guy Jin messing around.
Did you film your intimate scenes?
Filming them right now.
Are there no cameras in this room?
Wouldn't it be better if there were?
Judging by your energy,
you haven't filmed them yet.
Saving it all up to use on you.
Let's talk business.
I want to give the money
from the next magazine to Jin.
To who?
Jin Lifeng.
Wait, did I hear that right?
That's him.
He's the one who arranged the
intimate scenes in your drama.
If we give him money,
he'll cut the scenes...?
Not necessarily.
Then are you an idiot?
I told him.
You're not adding any scenes.
And we're giving him the magazine money.
No, Han Lu.
I'm having a hard time
following your logic here.
I don't quite get it.
Is it that you can't accept me
shooting intimate scenes with someone else,
or do you just think we have
too much money right now
and you have to throw it away?
I have my reasons.
Why? I'm asking you, why?
The money we worked so hard to earn,
you want to give to someone
who isn't short on cash at all?
You're really spoiling him.
Are you trying to make me lose everything?
Hear me out.
Even Sister Jialin couldn't
dig up his background.
If she can't find anything,
it means he's unfathomable.
Which means we can't afford to cross him.
Guys like him don't lack money,
and they certainly don't lack people.
He's only fixated on
me for the novelty of it.
Then let him have his fill of novelty!
Are you even listening to yourself?
I just don't understand.
Why does he get to take my money?
Don't get trapped in your own head.
Step back and look at the big picture.
We give him the money,
like giving a red envelope to a boss.
The boss doesn't need the money,
but they like the
feeling of receiving gifts.
Only by emotionally soothing his
resentment of not getting what he wants
can we truly shake him off.
I don't think so.
What if he keeps pestering you?
To deal with people like him,
we have to fight fire with fire.
There's no other way around it.
But we don't have the
power to fight fire with fire.
Even if we take him down,
there will be an even greater evil later.
We can only defuse the situation.
Defusing it is our way of survival.
Fine.
Then I think you should just
let him have his fill of novelty.
Once he's had enough,
everything will be defused.
Unlocked successfully.
Please open the door.
I just got back from the temple.
I smell heavily of incense.
I'm going up to the second floor to change.
Make yourself at home.
What would you like to drink?
Do you have coffee?
You asked the right person.
The best Tianyi coffee.
Brother Lang.
Yeah?
There are some things I want to
ask someone who's been through it.
Troubles?
Unspoken rules.
What makes you so
sure I've been through it?
At least everyone thinks
that someone who hasn't been through it
could never make it in
the entertainment industry.
Fair enough.
Tell me about your troubles.
This is your trouble.
This is the solution you chose.
This is Qi Haoyu.
And there are many
others you didn't choose.
If life is a straight line,
connecting it this way or that way
will definitely lead to
two different outcomes.
So if we keep making assumptions,
all we can see are
two paths drifting further apart.
Take away the assumptions,
and it goes back to what
Sister Lan always says.
Don't make preconceived notions.
Before the outcome happens,
everything is just an assumption.
What if the outcome is bad?
But right now, you can't
predict the outcome at all.
Will you even think it's
bad once it happens?
That's a bit convoluted.
For example, seven years
ago when I was with Shi Yuhao,
I thought breaking up
would be the worst outcome.
But I never expected
that seven years later,
I'd meet someone else, and looking back,
what I originally defined
as the worst outcome
actually looks pretty good.
Give the magazine money
to whoever you want.
Thank you.
Director Ou said it very well.
Our movie "Rumination" is
a gaze upon life.
Let's immerse ourselves together.
We're dominating the charts. The
trending topics are all about our company.
How did these few shoot up?
At first, it seemed like they were bought,
but now it's all organic traffic.
Suppress the love story one immediately.
[The "love story" between the two bosses]
Got it, I'll arrange it.
Ms. Fang, another one just shot up.
Jialan's daughter and gene customization.
This one is rising fast.
Go prepare the supporting documents first.
Ask Lawyer Shang to draft a legal letter.
Have the PR firm control the comments ASAP.
Ms. Fang, proving our
innocence won't do much good.
I know.
The company's artists should
speak up and take a stand now.
What if the ship sinks?
[Many comments all damning the rich and
their choices while lamenting being poor]
[Fans asking what the meaning behind the post is]
["Stop the rumours!" ad nauseum]
Shit.
That's freaking awesome.
Hey.
A food blogger uploaded a
dish called "All-Sorts Shrimp."
It's already hit the
top of the trending list.
Lang Di, your bait-and-switch
move is brilliant.
Log into my main
account and give it a like.
Sure.
["Upright bodies aren't scared
of tilted shadows" ad nauseum]
Come on, everyone
look at me. Ready, 1, 2, 3.
[The comments repeating a proverb of
essentially "Good people keep good company"]
[Comments stating that the genetic modifcation was
a rumor, the company stays on top of the search]
I was organizing my cloud drive today
and stumbled upon this old photo.
Do you guys remember which movie
and which scene this is from?
That summer,
we shot a movie celebrating youth together.
The weather in the south was hot and humid.
As soon as I arrived on set, I
broke out in a full-body rash.
After filming wrapped and
we entered post-production,
the producer, Sister
Lan, sent me a screenshot.
Yes, this exact one.
Big and small red rashes all over my body.
Sister Lan said she counted
over a hundred of them.
Sister Lan scolded me back then,
saying I drank eight
cups of iced coffee a day,
chain-smoked,
and didn't take care of my body.
She said my hormones were out of
whack, which caused the breakout.
The footage that needed to be processed
for the whole film was over an hour long.
The post-production budget for
skin-smoothing VFX was going to hit 600,000.
I didn't think much of it at the time.
Then, four months
later, I saw the final cut.
There wasn't a single red rash on my body,
and the footage wasn't overly smoothed out.
Sister Lan said
she and Sister Jialin spent four months
smoothing it out frame by
frame. 25 frames per second.
One frame is one picture.
An hour of video equals 90,000 pictures.
They spent four months
retouching exactly 90,000 pictures.
To ensure there were no skipped frames,
every rash and acne mark had
to be smoothed out in order,
from beginning to end.
That's way more than just
90,000 pictures' worth of work.
Ms. Fang, Shi Yuhao spoke up for us.
The tide is turning.
They only slept four hours a day,
staring at the screen until
they cried from exhaustion.
Their eyes were searching
for red spots on my body.
Just turning their heads
made their vision blur.
Who with money would willingly
put themselves through that?
Back then, they and we
had absolutely nothing.
["Gods Have Come to Humanity"]
Sister Lan, the novel you
definitely wished for is getting filmed,
now even more people
will see your first intention]
[Fans commenting
about the adaptation]
Release the synopsis for Canghuang.
Post the concept posters
and the director's statement.
Release them every hour on the hour.
This is more intense
than a war. It's so thrilling!
Canghuang Synopsis.
Sister Jialin followed
up with a great move.
Canghuang tells the story of the greatest
king in the history of the Qi Kingdom,
King Ran Huang, who, to
control human genetic pollution,
formed a global army called
the Sea Expeditionary Force.
The Sea God, Bai Jinghua,
served as its first commander.
One man and one god worked together
to create a balanced
world in this Xianxia tale.
[insane gay laugh]
Who would have thought our Xianxia drama
would have an anti-gene
customization theme?
Sister Lan, you're truly something else.
So ahead of your time.
Fourteen years ahead of humanity.
Sister Lan.
I miss you so much.
[Top search is about the company
mobilizing to make a new fantasy show]
[Han Lu]
Lu.
Are you home?
Brother Guo.
Some people
are too scared to go home themselves,
so they use me as a shield.
Come in, you useless piece of work.
Oh, our indispensable
hero returns in triumph!
Damn, my pot is growing mold.
You two
are both solving problems in your own ways.
But what matters isn't
whose method is right,
but that you both have the heart
to make things better together.
You have it, and so does he.
So there's nothing wrong with that.
Brother Guo.
You have no idea how he chewed me out.
Brother, this is how I chewed him out.
Oh, enough.
Go wash your moldy pot.
Fine.
Haoyu bringing up Sister
Lan's early works this time
was indeed the most crucial
step in resolving the crisis.
You have to admit his intentions were good.
But his attitude was terrible.
Hey, a bad attitude can be corrected.
But if the heart is crooked,
there's no saving it.
Who are you calling crooked?
Oh, knock it off.
A broken pot can't shut a
trashy mouth. Go wash the pot.
Fine.
As for what needed to be said,
I think I've already said it all.
You two can settle the rest in bed.
Let me feed you.
Qi Haoyu, back off.
Your mouth is filthy.
Filthy or not, you've
kissed it plenty. Come here.
Is it sweet?
Sweet.
Have another bite.
Mom, I'm going to become a monk.
Do you remember when you
took me to the temple as a kid?
A master saw me and said,
"This child will return sooner or later."
When Jianjun passed
away, Tian was still little.
I had to stay in the mortal
world a few more years.
Now that I see Lang has
someone to take care of him,
and you have Lang to take care of you,
it's time for me to go back.
I don't want Tian to
be lonely up in heaven.
I'm going to the temple
to chant sutras for him.
He likes listening to them.
He can hear them.
Since he likes it, I should chant
for him more while I'm still alive.
Go ahead.
Mom is still going strong.
I don't need you.
It's truly a tragedy for a
parent to bury their child.
[Changyang At Home]
[Mom has decided to become a nun]
Is it him?
I can't see clearly.
It's definitely him, no mistake about it.
Auntie, let me tell you.
I've compared it with
your photo so many times.
They look exactly the same.
Auntie.
We can't let my brother die in vain.
Hey, listen to me.
I've looked into this movie.
That little boy is the lead actor.
And the director won some kind of award.
Anyway, this movie got a lot of
traffic as soon as it was released.
Do you know what traffic means?
Traffic means money, Auntie.
Hey, let me tell you.
You and Uncle don't need
to worry about a thing.
Leave everything to me.
What do you need to do?
Sit back, talk, and collect the money.
Before my son got into the car accident,
he came back and told us
that he liked men.
It was this person.
He looks neither like a man nor a woman.
He seduced my son.
I'll write a script for you tomorrow.
Director Li, you flatter me too much.
But I really can't give
you an answer right now.
I'm also still waiting for news.
Do you have other acting offers?
No.
My friend led a team
into the primeval forest.
There's no signal right now.
I can't reach him either.
I have to wait until he comes out
and discuss it with him
before I can give you an answer.
A very important friend?
Yes.
Director Li, rest assured.
If I take on any roles in
the second half of the year,
it will definitely be yours.
Old man.
The director from my last show
has already deleted that intimate scene.
It's already been filmed.
I badgered him for days
before the director finally agreed.
It was just shot with camera tricks.
Shot with camera tricks?
It must look awful.
Did you really need to badger him?
You're so full of hot air.
Not a single word of truth. I'm hanging up.
Sister Jialin.
You're back.
Yeah. Don't tell Qinglang I'm back.
There's absolutely nothing
wrong with this car. Look.
Earth Pay OK?
Okay.
Auntie, I'll have this apple here.
Auntie.
I've paid, Auntie.
[Haiyuan Hostel]
Season 2 of "Still a
Teenager Upon Return" is
title-sponsored by the Hot Love brand.
Entering Xizhou.
Still a Teenager Upon Return.
With the wind and moon as witnesses,
wishing you peace deep in
your bones year after year.
We're discussing an
endorsement next Tuesday.
I'll send you the location.
Drive yourself over.
[On a call with Vicky the Agent]
The variety show with
you two is really popular.
A few new endorsement offers
came in. Do you want to take them?
You arrange it.
No joint endorsements.
(Changyang at Home)
(Someone in June, is
the assessment over? ~)
When you need me the most,
I can't be by your side,
nor can I message you in real-time.
But I'll write messages in
advance and schedule them for you.
I promise you'll receive a
message from me every day.
We'll never lose touch
for the rest of our lives.
(Feng Qinglang: Can you really
do it just because you promise?)
I bet when you saw yesterday's
message, you definitely said,
"Can you really do it just
because you promise?"
Maybe due to outside
interference, I might not be able to.
But when I made the promise,
my heart was bound to making it happen.
(You're bound to making it happen,
so do you want to seperate from me?)
Let me guess
what you'll say when you
see yesterday's message.
You've read too many scripts.
Someone who loves to nitpick words
will definitely make a fuss about "bound."
A petty person would get jealous of
me being bound to something else.
I know, I need to correct my
last sentence from yesterday.
My heart can only ever be bound to you.
While I'm at it, let me predict
what you'll say today.
"Am I petty?"
You guessed wrong. Today I want to say,
I miss you so much.